<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-10-25T13:55:36+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">pablocalvo</title><subtitle>personal blog for everythng that I want to write about -  work, family, sports, life. subscribe if you like it, email me if you don't.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Life works in misterious ways</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/personal/2019/10/25/life-is-a-matter-of-perspective.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Life works in misterious ways" /><published>2019-10-25T11:51:10+02:00</published><updated>2019-10-25T11:51:10+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/personal/2019/10/25/life-is-a-matter-of-perspective</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/personal/2019/10/25/life-is-a-matter-of-perspective.html">&lt;p&gt;I have been working extra these days so my wife has to also work extra and take care of the babies, me and helself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I went to the supermarket after a rough night of overworking, I was like: “Oh I am going to buy her a coke, or a chocolate, something nice for being there”.
so I picked a lot of stuff: fruits, some nice lunch, icecream, coke, chocolate (yeah suhar), and when I went to pay it was a bill of €26, but I couldn’t pay.
And I did several attempts, but the pos was not picking my card, so I had to return everything and walk with the hands empty, the shame and sadness on my face
and also late for work.
&lt;em&gt;Apparently I had only €25 on the bank. €1 more and I could buy everything.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I went again with a different card, I bought everything, but it was magical: it was the same cashier lady from yesterday, she looked at me, I looked at her,
she slowly passed the products on the reader, she looked at me again, it was again €28, I insert the other card today, then…. no error, everything went fine,
she started smiling a look, and said some funny things on German (I live in Berlin, but I don’t speak the language), she smiled more, almost laughed, she 
had a moment of joy. this only happened because of a bad experience the last day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Life works in misterious ways!!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I have been working extra these days so my wife has to also work extra and take care of the babies, me and helself.</summary></entry></feed>